stylefactoryproductions.com 2019-07-10

# Privacy notice — Style Factory Web Design and E-Commerce

**INTRODUCTION**   

Welcome to the Style Factory Communications Ltd privacy notice for [www.stylefactoryproductions.com/](http://www.meantimecomms.com/).

Style Factory Communications Ltd (company number 10232963) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal data. This privacy notice will inform you as to how we look after your personal data when you visit our website (regardless of where you visit it from) and tell you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.   

Please also use the Glossary to understand the meaning of some of the terms used in this privacy notice.

1\. IMPORTANT INFORMATION AND WHO WE ARE  
2\. THE DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU  
3\. HOW IS YOUR PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED  
4\. HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA  
5\. DISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA  
6\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS  
7\. DATA SECURITY  
8\. DATA RETENTION  
9\. YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS  
10\. GLOSSARY  

 **1.**    **IMPORTANT INFORMATION AND WHO WE ARE**   

 **PURPOSE OF THIS PRIVACY NOTICE**   

This privacy notice aims to give you information on how Style Factory Communications Ltd collects and processes your personal data through your use of this website and our services, including any data you may provide through this website, including (but not limited to) any data you may provide through this website when you sign up to our mailing lists, purchase a product or service from us, or become a customer of Style Factory Communications Ltd.    

This website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.

It is important that you read this privacy notice together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy notice supplements the other notices and is not intended to override them.

 **CONTROLLER**   

Style Factory Communications Ltd (referred to as “we”, “us” or “our” in this privacy notice) is the ‘controller’ of your personal data and responsible for your personal data. This privacy notice is issued on behalf of Style Factory Communications Ltd.

 **CONTACT DETAILS**   

Our full contact details are here:

Full name of legal entity: Style Factory Communications Ltd

Postal address: Kemp House, 152 City Road, London EC1V 2NX

You can email us via our [contact form](https://www.stylefactoryproductions.com/contact/).

If you have any questions about this privacy notice or our practices and procedures in relation to your personal data, or if you want to exercise your legal rights, please contact us the using the details set out above. We would appreciate the chance to deal with any concerns you might have but you have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues ([ _www.ico.org.uk_](http://www.ico.org.uk/)). 

 **CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY NOTICE AND YOUR DUTY TO INFORM US OF CHANGES**   

This version was last updated on 13 August 2018. 

It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes during your relationship with us.

 **THIRD-PARTY LINKS**   

This website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications (including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, Instagram and Google+). Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy notices or statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every website you visit.

 **2.**    **THE DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU**   

Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (ie anonymous data).

We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped together as follows: 

  *  **Identity Data** includes first name, last name, username or similar identifier, title.
  *  **Contact Data** includes billing address, email address and telephone numbers.
  *  **Financial Data** includes bank account and payment card details.
  *  **Transaction Data** includes details about payments to and from you and other details of products and services you have purchased from us. 
  *  **Technical Data** includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.
  *  **Profile Data** includes **** any username and password, purchases or orders made by you, your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses.
  *  **Usage Data** includes information about how you use our website, products and services.
  *  **Marketing and Communications Data** includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.

We also collect, use and share **Aggregated Data** such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose. Aggregated Data may be derived from your personal data but is not considered personal data in law as this data does **not** directly or indirectly reveal your identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific website page or feature. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated Data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this privacy notice.

 **IF YOU FAIL TO PROVIDE PERSONAL DATA**   

Where we need to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have with you and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you (for example, to provide you with products or services). In this case, we may have to cancel a product or service you have with us but we will notify you if this is the case at the time.

 **3.**    **HOW IS YOUR PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED?**   

We use different methods to collect data from and about you including through:

 **Direct interactions.** You may give us your Identity, Contact and Financial Data through our website or by corresponding with us by post, phone, email or otherwise. This includes personal data you provide when you:

  * enquire about our products or services;
  * subscribe to our service or publications;
  * request marketing information to be sent to you;
  * enter a competition, promotion or survey; or
  * give us some feedback.

 **Automated technologies or interactions.** As you interact with our website, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your device, browsing actions and patterns. We may collect this personal data by using cookies, server logs and other similar technologies. We may also receive Technical Data about you if you visit other websites employing our cookies.

 **Third parties or publicly available sources.** We may receive personal data about you from various third parties including marketing services providers and partner organisations and public sources.

 **4.**    **HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**   

We will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:

  * Where we have your consent to do so.
  * Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you.
  * here it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.
  * Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.

Generally we do not rely on consent as a legal basis for processing your personal data. You have the right to withdraw consent to marketing at any time by contacting us.

 **PURPOSES FOR WHICH WE WILL USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**   

We have set out below, in a table format, a description of the ways we plan to use your personal data, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate. You can find out more about these in the glossary in section 10 of this privacy notice. 

Note that we may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. Please contact us if you need details about the specific legal ground we are relying on to process your personal data where more than one ground has been set out in the table below.

 **MARKETING AND INSIGHTS**   

We strive to provide you with choices regarding certain personal data uses, particularly around marketing and advertising.

Where you have given your consent (where lawfully required), we use cookies, log files and other technologies to collect personal information from the device you use to access our website. This may include Technical Data as referred to in section 2 above.

We may use “cookies” "web beacons" or “pixel tags” (“Tags”) and mobile identifiers. Tags allow us to track receipt of an e-mail to you, to count users that have visited a webpage or opened an e-mail and collect other types of aggregate information. Once you click on an e-mail that contains a Tag, your contact information may subsequently be cross-referenced to the source e-mail and the relevant Tag. In some of our e-mail messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to certain websites administered by us or on our behalf. See our [Cookie Notice](https://www.stylefactoryproductions.com/cookie-policy) for more details.

 **PROMOTIONAL OFFERS FROM US**   

We may use your Identity, Contact, Technical, Usage and Profile Data to form a view on what we think you may want or need, or what may be of interest to you. This is how we decide which products, services and offers may be relevant for you (we call this marketing).

You will receive marketing communications from us if you have requested information from us or purchased products or services from us or if you provided us with your details when you entered a competition or registered for a promotion and, in each case, where it is lawful for us to provide that marketing communication to you. 

 **THIRD-PARTY MARKETING**   

We will get your express opt-in consent before we share your personal data with any company outside Style Factory Communications Ltd for marketing purposes.

 **OPTING OUT**   

You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing communications at any time by following the opt-out links on any marketing message sent to you or by contacting us at any time.

 **COOKIES**   

You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may become inaccessible or not function properly. 

 **CHANGE OF PURPOSE**   

We will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you would like an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us.

Please note that we may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.

 **5.**    **DISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA**   

We may have to share your personal data with the parties set out below for the purposes set out in the table in paragraph 4 above.

  * Third Parties as set out in the _Glossary_.
  * Third parties to whom we may choose to sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets. Alternatively, we may seek to acquire other businesses or merge with them. If a change happens to our business, then the new owners may use your personal data in the same way as set out in this privacy notice.

We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

 **6.**    **INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS**   

Personal data is currently stored via [Squarespace](https://www.squarespace.com/), [Getresponse](https://www.getresponse.com/) and [Google (G Suite)](https://gsuite.google.co.uk/intl/en_uk/).

Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is implemented:

  * We will only transfer your personal data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission. For further details, see [_European Commission: Adequacy of the protection of personal data in non-EU countries_](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/adequacy-protection-personal-data-non-eu-countries_en).
  * Where we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe. For further details, see [_European Commission: Model contracts for the transfer of personal data to third countries_](https://ec.europa.eu/info/strategy/justice-and-fundamental-rights/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/model-contracts-transfer-personal-data-third-countries_en).
  * Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between the Europe and the US. For further details, see [_European Commission: EU-US Privacy Shield_](https://ec.europa.eu/info/strategy/justice-and-fundamental-rights/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/eu-us-privacy-shield_en).

Please contact us if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your personal data out of the EEA.

 **7.**    **DATA SECURITY**   

We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

 **8.   DATA RETENTION  **

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

In some circumstances you can ask us to delete your data: see the section below on your rights for further information.

 **9.   YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS  **

You have the following rights in relation to the personal data we hold about you. Please note that these rights are subject to certain exemptions which may be applicable to any request you make.

 **Your right of access**

 _If you ask us, we’ll confirm whether we’re processing your personal information and, subject to any applicable exemptions, provide you with a copy of that personal information (along with certain other details) within the timescales or extended timescales provided for by the GDPR for complex requests, or where applicable, provide you with an explanation as to why we will not be complying with your request. If you require additional copies, we may need to charge a reasonable fee._

 **Your right to rectification**

 _If the personal information we hold about you is inaccurate or incomplete, you’re entitled to have it rectified. If you are entitled to rectification and if we’ve shared your personal information with others, we’ll let them know about the rectification where possible and where this would not involve disproportionate effort. If you ask us, where possible and lawful to do so, we’ll also tell you who we’ve shared your personal information with so that you can contact them directly._

 **Your right to erasure**

 _You can ask us to delete or remove your personal information in some circumstances such as where we no longer need it or if you withdraw your consent (where applicable because that was the legal basis on which we were processing your personal information). If you are entitled to erasure and if we’ve shared your personal information with others, we’ll take reasonable steps to inform those others where possible and where this would not involve disproportionate effort. If you ask us, where it is possible and lawful for us to do so, we’ll also tell you who we’ve shared your personal information with so that you can contact them directly._

 **Your right to restrict processing**

 _You can ask us to ‘block’ or suppress the processing of your personal information in certain circumstances such as where you contest the accuracy of that personal information or you object to us. If you are entitled to restriction and if we’ve shared your personal information with others, we’ll let them know about the restriction where it is possible for us to do so. If you ask us, where it is possible and lawful for us to do so, we’ll also tell you who we’ve shared your personal information with so that you can contact them directly._

 **Your right to data portability**

 _With effect from 25 May 2018, you have the right, in certain circumstances, to obtain personal information you’ve provided us with (in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format) and to reuse it elsewhere or to ask us to transfer this to a third party of your choice._

 **Your right to object**

 _You can ask us to stop processing your personal information, and we will do so, if we are:_

 _relying on our own or someone else’s legitimate interests to process your personal information, except if we can demonstrate compelling legal grounds for the processing; or_

 _processing your personal information for direct marketing._

 **Your rights in relation to automated decision-making and profiling**

 _You have the right not to be subject to a decision when it’s based on automatic processing, including profiling, if it produces a legal effect or similarly significantly affects you, unless such profiling is necessary for entering into, or the performance of, a contract between you and us._

 **Your right to withdraw consent _ _**

 _If we rely on your consent (or explicit consent) as our legal basis for processing your personal information, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time.  _

If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please contact us.

 **NO FEE USUALLY REQUIRED**   

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these or any other circumstances where lawfully entitled to do so.

 **WHAT WE MAY NEED FROM YOU**   

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.

 **TIME LIMIT TO RESPOND**   

We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.

 **10.**    **GLOSSARY**   

 **LAWFUL BASIS**   

 **Legitimate Interest** means the legitimate interest of us or any third party eg in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best service/product and the best and most secure experience. We make sure we consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative) and your rights before we process your personal data for our legitimate interests. We do not use your personal data for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law). You can obtain further information about how we assess our legitimate interests against any potential impact on you in respect of specific activities by _Contacting us_ _._

 **Performance of Contract** means processing your personal data where it is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or to take steps at your request before entering into such a contract.

 **Comply with a legal obligation** means processing your personal data where it is necessary for compliance with a legal or regulatory obligation that we are subject to.

 **THIRD PARTIES**   

  * Service providers based within and outside the EEA who help us to provide products and services to you, including those helping us to administer and protect our business, maintain the safety, security and integrity of our services and/or our website (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data, research, analysis and product development and the provision of IT and system administration services).
  * Professional advisers including lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers based within the EEA who provide consultancy, banking, legal, insurance and accounting services.
  * Regulators and other authorities who require reporting of our activities in certain circumstances.
  * Software / app providers — we use [Squarespace](https://www.squarespace.com/), [Getresponse](https://www.getresponse.com/) and [Google (G Suite)](https://gsuite.google.co.uk/intl/en_uk/) to capture and/or store personal details.
